hifivision.com 2013-08-12

# Privacy Policy - HiFiVision.com - Audio Video Hi-Fi Forum

Notices  
---  
  
Hello and Welcome to **www.HiFiVision.com** \- an online discussion forum for the audio video home theatre and hi-fi enthusiasts!

The objective of this forum is to provide a platform for all audio and video enthusiasts to share, discuss and express their views, opinions and experience in Audio Video Home Threate Consumer Electronics and Hi-Fi with one another. It does not matter if you are novice or a veteran, enjoy music or movies, swear by horn speakers or tube amplifiers, LCD or Plasma, at HiFiVision.com we all share one common goal and that is to enhance our audio/visual and/or listening/viewing experience.

If this is your first time here please register yourself. Registration is fast, simple and absolutely **free** so please, **join our community today**! 

If you have any problems with the registration process or your account login, please read the [FAQ](http://www.hifivision.com/faq.php?faq=vb_faq#faq_help_for_new_users).  

[Advertise Here](http://www.hifivision.com/ads/index.php?loc=view_adrates&uid=100000) Privacy Policy  
---  
  
  * www.HiFiVision.com recognizes that you care about the personal information that is held about you and how that is used.
  * This privacy policy applies to all personal data, submitted by you, to the www.HiFiVision.com web site.
  * By registering to www.HiFiVision.com you need to submit a chosen name and contact information, more specifically an e-mail address.
  * www.HiFiVision.com also stores and reads cookies to and from your computer. Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that we transfer to your computer's hard drive through your Web browser to enable our forums and general website features to recognize your browser for when you return to this web site. By using this website, you agree that both the webserver, and any trusted 3rd party we chose, such as advertising networks, may place a tracking cookie on your machine and access it at any time during your session. These cookies will enable third party advertising networks like Google to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site and other sites on the Internet. You can opt out of the [DoubleClick DART cookie](http://www.doubleclick.com/privacy/faq.aspx) cookie served by Google at any time by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html). In general, cookies are safe and are not a security issue when being used from 'trusted' internet sites, such as www.HiFiVision.com. For information on how to manage cookies in your browser, please visit [AboutCookies.org](http://www.aboutcookies.org/Default.aspx?page=2)
  * www.HiFiVision.com will not sell, transmit or distribute any data held without your prior permission or consent, unless required to do so under relevant law.
  * All other information provided by you goes into a "public profile" and is entirely optional, all information held in that profile is held there at your own risk. This info is edited via your Control Panel in the forums.
  * You have a legal right for the personal information held at www.HiFiVision.com to be updated if it is incorrect or deleted if you choose. Most of this can be done through your Control Panel in the forums. If you are having issues with this, please contact us if you need help.
  * www.HiFiVision.com will take all reasonable effort to ensure that all personal information about you submitted is maintained secure on our server. However, we make no warranty to this.
  * This site is intended for individuals over the age of 13. Any information collected is intended to be of individuals over the age of 13. According to [COPPA](http://www.ftc.gov/coppa/index.html), our site does NOT cater to children. "Operators of commercial websites or online services directed to children under 13 that collect personal information from children" require a COPPA agreement and privacy policy. Since we do not cater to this age group, no COPPA exists on www.HiFiVision.com
  * This Privacy Policy may be modified at any time without notice. It is your responsibility to check this page for updates or changes. 

All times are GMT +5.5. The time now is 07:29 PM.
